A little pause... and we are back.
I commend all those
who have advanced to the
finals for the third level
of the tuning exams.
Well, there's one person missing,
but still, congratulations.
Sensei?
Hmm?
I have a question for you.
About Sasuke?
I'm sorry.
I don't know much about that, I'm afraid.
But I wouldn't worry too much.
From here on, it's up to you, Sasuke.
Sakura, I have to leave, so I'm counting
on you to get the details about the finals.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Here, including the absent Sasuke,
we have five ninja from the Leaf Village.
Three from the Sand Village.
And one from the Sound Village.
And now I will begin the explanation of
the final rounds.
Well, it's about time.
The preliminaries are done.
They're moving on to the final rounds.
While all these countries are busy racing
to expand their military might,
the birds are still singing.
I believe that this country of ours has
been at peace for far, far too long.
Then let me do it.
Hmm.
I don't know.
How much fun would it be to take out an
old man like the Hokage, anyway?
What's the problem?
You're not still having second thoughts
about it, are you, Orochimaru?
From now on, each of the
hidden villages will clash
with each other in a
long and violent struggle.
Even the Sound Village won't escape that
violence.
And it's your intention to be the trigger
for all that hostility.
By using Sasuke as a bullet?
Isn't that correct?
Hmm.
You guess very well.
So well that it's a bit creepy,
in fact.
The curse mark that was given to him
appears to have been sealed by Kakashi.
But in any event, that is not my concern.
While there is still some darkness left in
his heart, we must act.
And that's why I want you to abduct him.
It's unusual for you to act so hastily,
is it not?
Perhaps.
But there's still a little something
that's troubling me.
Is it Naruto Uzumaki?
Hmm.
You're quite sharp, aren't you,
Kabuto?
According to your
information, contact with that
nine-tailed one has altered
Sasuke's heart and mind.
So much so that Naruto now holds a certain
influence over our Sasuke.
The thing to do is to get Sasuke away from
him immediately.
Because then... It will be so
easy to make him mine forever.
Very well.
Hmm.
That face...
I wonder what's going on in his head.
In the final rounds, each of you will put
your battle skills on display.
You'll demonstrate the
power and control that
you've achieved in your
respective disciplines.
Accordingly, the final battles will
commence one month from now.
Wait, we're not gonna do it right here and
now?
This is to provide a suitable period of
preparation.
What do you mean by that?
Simply this.
In addition to announcing the conclusion
of the preliminary matches to each
country's leaders, we must
also have some time to prepare
and distribute the summons
for the final selection.
Not to mention that
you examinees are going
to need time to prepare
for something else.
Something that is this important.
This old man sure likes to beat around the
bush.
Look, I don't really get what you're
trying to say.
What's the point of this?
I mean that to know your adversaries and
prepare yourselves, you need time.
Even though up to this point all the
battles have been real battles,
as I'm sure you can all
attest, they were conducted on
the premise that you were
fighting an unknown enemy.
But that's no longer the case now that
you've battled each other.
Yeah, seriously.
I would never have dreamed that this guy
could turn sand into a weapon.
So in order to make the finals fair and
just, we're giving you this month,
each of you must embrace the opportunity
to practice hard and learn some new tricks.
Because by now everyone here
knows your techniques, so using
your old tired tricks is a
sure way to lose in the finals.
And remember to get some rest as well.
This isn't some vacation!
I won't have any time to relax!
I've got to train harder than ever!
I suppose brilliance can sometimes have
its disadvantages.
We failed to avoid
Orochimaru's watchful eye,
and it's most
unfortunate for both of us.
He's so young, but
the seeds of evil have
already taken root just
waiting to be exploited.
He'll be ripe for Orochimaru's special
ninjutsu.
Well, well, Kakashi.
Foiling my attack by striking from my
blind spot, huh?
But now, are you ready to take me on?
Next time you should station at least ten
guards.
The Anbu Black Ops unit that I assembled
was defeated so easily.
You... you're not an ordinary genin,
are you?
You caught a whiff of me and immediately
readied your weapon.
Quite impressive.
You overestimate me.
So what do you want with Sasuke?
Finding you like this, I ought to haul you
in for questioning.
What, just you?
I wonder if you could.
Are you looking to take me on?
Yes, I am.
I know who you are.
You're the Leaf Medical Corps Chief's son.
Your name... what was it?
Kabuto Yakushi.
What are you, one of Orochimaru's puppets?
Even if you did take me
into custody, you'd never
be able to prove I have
any connection to him.
Just answer my question.
And if I say no?
I'm the one asking the questions.
Now give me some answers.
Look, you'll have your answers soon
enough, even if I'm not here.
So why don't we skip the middleman and let
me go?
You smart-alecky little brat.
I'll teach you to mess around with
grown-ups.
Come on, give me a break.
Don't be so arrogant.
The cards are clearly in my favor here.
Let's go.
I can't believe I let him escape.
Impressive.
Just as I suspected, the Dead Soul Jutsu,
where a ninja temporarily animates and
controls a dead body, even transforming
its face.
Kabuto even stopped his own heart and
eliminated all traces of his scent in
order to escape by impersonating a
murdered Anbu Black Ops ninja.
Being raised as the
adopted son of the Chief of
the Medical Corps is
a powerful asset of his.
If it turns out that someone as good as
him is working for Orochimaru,
I've got to work harder.
Now, with all of that behind us,
I'd like to begin winding things up.
But before we can bring this
to an end, first there is one
more important matter to
take care of for the final rounds.
Let's get on with it!
I mean, come on!
How long do we have to wait until we start
training?
In a calm, orderly fashion,
all of you are going to take
one slip of paper from the
box that Anko is holding.
Everyone just stay where you are.
I'll come to you.
Just take one.
Hmm?
Good.
Now everyone has one.
Going from left to right, tell me the
number that's written on your slip of paper.
I've got eight.
Number one, of course.
Seven.
Five.
Three.
Nine.
Two.
Six.
And that means Sasuke will be number four.
Right.
Very good.
Now I'm going to tell you about how the
final selection tournament is going to work.
Is that what the numbers are for?
Drawing lots?
Eviki, you may reveal which ninja have
been paired up.
Yes, sir.
I'll be waiting forever.
Is that all the final rounds are?
A tournament?
I have to fight an extra round?
I'll probably be expected to avenge
Choji's loss.
Man, I'm glad I'm not in the same half of
the draw as Gaara.
Sasuke Uchiha.
Perfect.
I've got Neji Hyuga?
Right off the bat?
This couldn't be any better!
May I ask you a question?
You may.
All right.
If this is a tournament, does that mean
there's only going to be one winner?
I mean, only one of us is going to be able
to become a Chunin, then?
Actually, it's quite the contrary.
There are going to be several judges for
the final rounds, including myself,
the Shinobi leaders, and the Kazekage,
the lords from the various countries that
ultimately will be assigning your missions
to you.
Through this tournament, these judges will
be able to make a third choice.
They will make a thorough evaluation of
your abilities.
They will then decide
whether any or all of
you possess the qualities
required of a Chunin.
Even if someone loses the first round,
they could still become a Chunin.
So there's actually a chance
that every one of us who
competes in the final
selection could become Chunin?
Correct.
But conversely, there's also a chance that
none of you will be chosen.
The advantage in fighting more
rounds in the tournament is in
getting more chances to
display your talents in front of you.
You are one of the judges who will decide
your fate.
Does that answer your question,
Shikamaru?
This is just about the biggest pain ever.
I thank you all for your patience.
Now let us adjourn until next month.
In the second round, will it be Sasuke or
that browless freak?
He's so strong he took down Bushibrow
without breaking a sweat!
You're one of the ones I want to fight the
most.
I need to ask Kakashi-sensei for help.
Lady Hanabi!
Terrible news!
I heard Elder Sister Hinata was injured.
She's been treated and is conscious now.
There's no need to worry.
She should have expected this outcome if
she chose to go up against Neji.
Why didn't you just withdraw?
I couldn't... do that.
I'm quite aware of exactly what I am,
you know?
I'm an indecisive failure.
But I don't want to give up.
I want to become strong.
I know that I can change.
Watching Naruto makes me think so.
Naruto... I don't want you here.
You're nothing but a pest!
But I wasn't even doing anything!
I mean, I was just looking at the masks
you have.
I never will go back on my word.
Because that's my ninja way.
Hey, where's Sasuke's room?
Sorry.
No visitors allowed.
What?
No visitors?
Are you kidding me?
Those are the rules.
Ah, come on, lady!
Naruto, this is a hospital.
Keep it down.
Huh?
Oh, Kakashi-sensei!
Boy, am I glad to see you!
I gotta ask you a favor!
Stop right there.
I already know what you're going to ask.
So I've been looking for someone that can
oversee your training for the final rounds.
Hold on!
Why can't you train me, sensei?
I have other matters to handle.
I don't have time to deal with you,
Naruto.
Hey!
Aha!
You're going to train Sasuke, aren't you,
Kakashi-sensei?
Now, now, don't complain.
Listen, I've found you an even better
teacher than me.
Well, who is it?
It is I!
You!
You closet pervert!
Such insolence.
What makes you say that?
I'm serious!
You should have seen him!
He saw my harem jutsu once and he fell to
pieces!
Harem jutsu?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a little joke we shared.
Look, I'll make you a deal.
Keep quiet about that and I'll buy you
anything you want to eat.
Barbecue, ramen, you name it.
Anything I want!
Well, well.
I had no idea you two were acquainted.
Yes, we go way back.
I still don't get why it has to be him.
I mean, anybody else.
Look, you, if it hadn't
been for Kakashi who asked
me this favor, I would
never consider training you.
Yeah?
Well, then don't!
Hey, hey, come on, you two.
Let's calm down.
Listen, Naruto, you're wrong about
Ebisu-sensei.
He's a special Jonin, a private tutor who
only trains the elite.
Frankly, he's a better teacher than I am.
Oh...
Anyway, Naruto, I've got to
say that of the three genin in
Squad 7, you're the one whose
basic skills need the most work.
That's what I want you to focus on this
time around.
Wait, hold on a second!
Are you honestly saying that I'm not as
good as Sasuke or Sakura?!
Naruto, no matter how
many skills you master,
the fundamentals
are, well, fundamental.
And yours could be improved.
So if you really want to become strong,
then just be quiet.
Be quiet and pay attention.
All right, Ebisu-sensei.
I leave him in your capable hands.
I'll do what I can.
I know it seems harsh, but trust me.
It's for your own good.
Just do your best.
Well, come on.
Let's get started.
Watch out!
Jump in, Choji!
Or it's like I'm only fighting Shikamaru!
Yeah, but if I do that, I'm just going to
hurt you, you know?
I'm stronger than you guys think.
Sorry, but I don't want to end up hurting
either one of you.
You really think you can fight better than
us?
Then go ahead!
Just try to hurt us!
Bring it on!
Come on, tough guy!
If you think you're so
strong... Hey, stop that!
You're hurting me!
Damn it.
He's such a drag.
Choji!
Are you being gentle simply because these
two are your friends?
Asuma-sensei, he just...
If that is the case, then you're
completely in the wrong here.
Sparring with a tough partner will only
help to make them stronger, so you'd
actually be doing them a favor by fighting
hard.
Huh?
Don't you understand that?
All right, then I'll show you.
Come on.
You and I are going to spar right now.
And if you're able to strike me even once,
then all of you will pass.
What's more, you have a whole hour to land
that blow.
But if you can't hit me,
Choji, then not only will you be
sent back to the academy,
but Ino and Shikamaru will too.
Seriously?
That's not fair!
Think of me as your enemy, and attack for
your sake as well as theirs.
Transform your kindness into strength.
One plain ramen and one miso ramen with
barbecue pork!
There you go.
Now, Naruto, having had a chance to
observe your technique first hand,
and going off what Kakashi
has told me, it's clear to
me that one of your weakest
points is chakra control.
Hmm?
Chakra control?
Exactly.
When we compare your abilities in this
department with those of your teammates,
Sakura and Sasuke, you're definitely
weaker.
As you may know, in order to successfully
perform ninjutsu, genjutsu, and the like,
a ninja must first build up his chakra.
Yeah, like you said!
I already know that!
I would hope so.
Well then, let's compare you to your
teammates in this department, and perhaps
you'll begin to see just how inferior your
abilities really are.
You've got an annoying way of putting
things.
As agreed, I'm buying you lunch.
So just be quiet and listen.
First, let's examine how Sakura prepares
for a clone jutsu.
Clone jutsu!
She's perfect at building up her chakra to
its full extent, and because she's so
efficient, she can make clones without
wasting any excess energy.
Cha-cha-cha!
As for Sasuke, it must be
said he's not nearly as efficient
when it comes to building
up a full supply of chakra.
Clone jutsu!
But you see, his control over the chakra
itself is so flawless that he has no
problem producing five clones as easily as
Sakura can.
So the result is the same, even if Sasuke
does waste more chakra in getting there.
What do you know?
And I thought Sasuke was perfect in
everything!
Wipe that smile off your face.
You are in no position to make fun of
anyone else.
Why?
You're no good at building up your chakra
or controlling it.
The result being you require much more
chakra to produce any clones.
What the...
You have to exert much more effort.
And even then, after all the effort,
and after wasting much more chakra than
either Sakura or
Sasuke... Clone jutsu!
You can barely produce two clones at best.
Sigh...
In fact, using the same amount of chakra
you use, Sakura can't produce any clones.
Sakura and Sasuke could come up with ten
clones.
Yeah, well if I'm such a
lame-o, how come there have
been times when I've
done better than they have?
That's not the same thing!
That's only because
you have reserves of
energy and stamina that
are hardly even human!
The point is, we both know
you're strong, Naruto, but you
could be so much stronger
if you'd let me show you how.
Really?
You mean it?
I not only mean it, I guarantee it.
Now if you're ready, let's begin.
Sir, your bill.
Oh, I forgot.
Naruto!
Thank you, come again!
Okay, you mind explaining why you've
dragged me up here to these hot springs?
Is a bath part of my training?
Not that I'd mind soaking my feet after
that hike.
Naruto!
Where do you think you're going?
That's the women's bath!
I will not allow any disreputable
behavior, young man!
What is it?
What's that look?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Anyway, what in the world are we doing
here?
Are you going to train me how to wash
behind my ears?
Not quite.
But you're right, it is part of your
training.
Hmm?
Right here.
This is the place.
A bath?
Okay, what's going on?
Don't take that tone with me.
Like I told you before, this is all part
of your training.
Okay, maybe you ought to try taking it
from the top.
What am I training for again?
I'm going to teach you how to walk... on
water.
Huh?
What is it now?
Do you seriously expect me to believe...
that you really know how to walk on water?
Of course I do!
According to what Kakashi told me,
you've already been trained in how to
climb a tree without using your hands,
right?
This is a variation of that.
I don't know.
That was a long time ago.
I'm not so good at remembering stuff that
far back.
Well, in tree climbing, the key is to
build up chakra in the points of contact,
and then to maintain it at a steady rate
of discharge.
Of course, trees are stationary objects,
so the discharge rate remains constant.
All the same, it's an excellent exercise
for developing basic chakra control.
Now, to walk on water, you not only have
to build up chakra at the points of
contact, you must also constantly adjust
the rate of discharge in order to maintain
your balance on the water's shifting
surface.
This is obviously more difficult than just
maintaining a fixed flow of chakra.
But that's what chakra control is all
about.
Being able to discharge it at a steady or
at a varying rate, you understand?
Hmm... I wish I did.
Well, perhaps it would be easier if I just
showed you.
First, build up chakra in the soles of
your feet.
Then, carefully calibrating
the amount you discharge
from each foot in order
to maintain your balance.
There, you see?
That's how it's done!
Cool!
Okay, let me give it a try now!
First, build up chakra in your feet.
And then, calibrating the
whatever it is... Not quite.
Oh, by the way, don't forget it's a hot
spring.
You don't want to keep falling in like
that.
You'll be boiled like a lobster.
Very funny!
I can do this!
Noooo!
Hot hot hot!
Well, you seem unusually diligent today,
Konohamaru.
Excellent, it looks like my guidance is
finally paying off.
Isn't it about time you were launching
another surprise attack against Lord Hokage?
Nah, I don't do that kind of thing
anymore.
That's astounding!
Well, I'm very glad to hear it.
So, you understand that the shortcut to
becoming Hokage is to do exactly as I say.
Well, there aren't any shortcuts here.
Huh?
Naruto told me that.
He said I had to learn that, if I ever
wanted to be Hokage.
Whoa!
I'm actually starting to get this!
Incredible!
He's right!
To think that he's already started to
master it!
I never imagined that he would have come
so far!
Indeed, there are no shortcuts in
anything.
Perhaps you were a better teacher to
Konohamaru than I was.
It seems I was wrong about you,
Naruto.
There is more within you than a demon's
spirit.
There is the heart of a splendid Hidden
Leaf Village ninja.
Ah!
Are you peaking in the women's bath,
old man?
I will not allow any disreputable
behavior!
Oh, please!
Huh?
What on earth?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Keep it down!
Do you want to get us busted, you idiot?
Huh?
Who is this guy?
He flattened my trainer!
And what's worse, he's an even bigger perv
than Ebisu!
Hehehe!
Hey, perv, you awake?
One way to find out!
Hidden Finger Jutsu!
Thousand years of death!
Man, he's totally out of it!
Some trainer, he's pathetic!
Okay, frogman, what was that all about?
Who do you think you are, anyway?
I'm glad you asked!
I'm the hermit of Mount Mayu-Boku,
the wise and immortal spirit!
That's right, it is I, the Toad Mountain
Sage!
What?
Toad Sage?
Exactly!
Toad Mountain Sage Toad Mountain Sage
Well, listen, you pervy sage!
What are you gonna do about this?
This guy is supposed to be training me, and
you laid him out flatter than a bath mat!
Well, he shouldn't have interfered with my
research.
Your research?
You see, I'm a novelist.
I am a writer of great books.
Like this!
Huh?
What?
You wrote that?
Yes!
I see you know it!
I'm famous, and it's not even out of
paperback yet!
You call that pervy trash a novel?
Research!
Yeah, right!
Just an excuse for you to peek at girls in
the bathhouse!
Look at what you've done!
You ruined my peeking!
I mean my research!
Dirty old man!
You little... There's
nothing dirty about it!
I happen to be a serious artist who's
inspired by youth and beauty, that's all!
And... Yeah, whatever.
Like anyone believes that!
Who cares anyway?
What about my training?
Hmm?
Your training?
You mean the walking on water technique
you were having so much trouble with?
You can do it?
Okay, then it's up to you to teach it to
me!
You at least owe me that!
Huh.
Stop bothering me, kid.
I'm busy.
Hey, wait!
Come back here, you pervy sage!
Where's your sense of responsibility?
You've gotta train me!
Not on your life!
I can't work with someone who has no
respect for a true artist!
Besides, I don't like kids.
Uh, actually, I thought your
book Make Out Paradise was,
uh, really well written, and
interesting, and informative!
Liar.
The purchase of reading of that book is
prohibited for anyone under the age of 18.
Oh, yeah, but the reviews I read were
great!
Do you really think that's going to work
on me?
What do you take me for, an idiot?
I'm a goddamn sage!
Save your breath, kid!
You can't butter me up!
Okay!
You're right!
Sorry, but wait,
you can't... Whoa!
So long and good luck!
That was cool!
I don't care if he is a dirty old man,
that guy's the real deal!
Come on, fight me!
Stop acting like such a coward!
That's not the way.
It'll just backfire.
Huh?
This whole thing isn't about Choji being
scared of fighting.
It's more that the last
thing he wants is to
hurt Asuma-sensei the
way he's hurting right now.
He's kind.
Right down to his very core.
But as things stand now...
Yeah, it seems we have no choice.
Hey, Choji!
Enough already!
Fight, fatso!
Hm?
Shimaru?
Did you just call me fatso?
Yeah, that's right.
I did call you fatso.
Because Asuma-sensei does.
Is that true, sensei?
That's right.
Sure is!
And he also said a fatso
like you would never be
able to land a punch
against him in a million years!
You're going overboard there, Ino.
Even if you're my sensei, anyone
who calls me that... ...is gonna get it!
I'm sorry, sensei.
But I can't do it.
I can't bring myself to hit you.
Please, sensei.
Only send me back to the academy,
okay?
Please don't punish Shimaru and Ino!
I understand, Choji.
We'll chalk this up as my loss.
No matter how angry you may become,
you're still able to suppress that feeling
and put yourself into your opponent's
shoes.
You have true kindness within you,
Choji.
I want you to keep nurturing that
kindness.
Because someday, it'll become your
greatest strength.
But you know, when you're sparring
with someone... Yeah, I know, sensei.
I don't want to beat people up like you or
Shimaru or Ino.
You know, my friends from the village.
But if I'm ever up against
anybody who wants to hurt my
friends, then I'm gonna fight
them with everything I've got!
Even if those friends like Shimaru and
Ino, who really know better than to push
me, keep calling me unpleasant names like
fatso!
Hmm...
You know, Shikamaru and Ino, he does have
a point.
Choji's not really fat, he's just...
pleasantly plump.
Oh,
what I'd give for just a few minutes with
a young, pretty girl.
You can't get rid of me that easy!
Well, what do you know?
A substitution jutsu!
Not bad, old man!
That was close.
Little squirt.
He'll have to be a lot smarter than that
to outfox the Toad Mountain Sage.
Oh yeah?
How am I doing now?
Okay, I'll admit you're not totally
without talent.
So does that mean you'll help me with my
training?
Not so fast, squirt.
It's a question of quid pro quo.
I'll give you what you want, but in return
you have to try and get me what I want.
So what do you want?
You must know by now.
I like them ripe and luscious with curves
like that, see?
And big, but not too big, know what I
mean?
If you bring me something like that,
I will train you till the cows come home!
You will?
No lie?
The Toad Mountain Sage never lies!
You got it!
Wait here!
Too bad, kid.
It's not like we had a contract.
Really?
Oh, ladies!
Can you show me the way to town?
Then I said, not with my rice bowl,
you don't!
That's a pretty funny story!
It's funny, yes, but it's not just a
story.
Every word of it is true.
Really?
What happened next?
Hey, Pervy Sage!
I'm back!
What?
Did he call you Pervy?
Worthless little runt!
I told you not to call me that!
Look!
I got you one!
Just the way you like them!
A ripe and luscious one with curves!
That's not what I meant, you moron!
Man, that was the best!
Struck out again.
No doubt about it.
It has to be!
Now I must be off.
I've wasted too much time already.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
What about my training?
We had a deal!
I don't give a flying fish for your
training!
I have my research to conduct!
Hmph!
Research my butt?
It's not like I don't
have better things to do
than hang around with
a pervy old coot like you!
I've gotta train till I'm stronger than
anyone!
Cause I'm gonna pass the Chunin exams!
And then someday, I'm gonna be Hokage!
Huh.
That's a good one.
Tell me, did you fall on your head when
you were a baby?
Is that what makes you this way?
Now I know you're wasting my time!
That's enough!
I need to get on with my research!
And for that, I need a lovely lady!
No fruits, no vegetables, but a lady!
A lady?
Oh, if that's what you wanted,
why didn't you just say so?
No problem!
Well, you know what you want!
Huff!
Mr. Worm!
Ah!
Oof... Ha!
Oof!
Oh my... Oh my...
Oh my... Oh my... Ah!
Oh my...
Oh my... Oh!
If you keep staring like that,
I'm going to blush.
She's just my type.
I really, really like her.
How did you do it?
Where on earth did she come from?
Oh, no biggie.
I call her my sexy jutsu.
Yeah, I love it.
You're a genius, kid.
This is one amazing technique.
Yeah, it seems to have that effect on a
lot of older guys.
So?
So, you'll help me with my training now,
right?
I'll do it if you promise.
To stay like that the whole time.
I was right!
You are pathetic!
You're nothing but a lousy little pervert!
I am not a little pervert!
Oh, yeah?
Then tell me, what are you?
I'm a big one.
Oh, great.
That makes all the difference.
Okay, we'll just pretend none of that
happened.
Now, let's begin your training.
And you really mean it this time?
A sage always means what he says.
Now, go ahead and show me that technique
you were working on before.
Okay.
Here goes!
You really do need help, don't you?
I should know by now to take my clothes
off first!
Hey, go on and build your chakra one more
time.
Can't I dry off a little first?
Now!
Do it!
So this is the formula used to imprison
the nine-tailed fox.
A double tetragram seal with an
eight-signed seal.
Huh.
That way, if any of the demon's chakra
escapes the tetragram seal, it will be
safely channeled into and suppressed by
the boy's own chakra.
But since then, a five-pronged seal has
been added.
An odd-numbered seal on top of an
even-numbered?
Hmm, that explains it.
That's why the boy's chakra and the
demon's are merging in an unstable way.
It's no wonder he can't control his chakra
very well.
Hehehe..
Cut it out!
What are you doing?
That tickles!
Hey, I don't want this on a big-time TV
show.
Okay,
raised your arms up high over your head.
Huh?
It's a trust exercise.
Come on!
Raise them high!
Five prong seal release!
What the heck was that for?
What?
Just pushing a pressure point to loosen
you up.
Now, go on.
Try walking on the water again.
Whoa, that's weird!
Look at that!
I'm doing it!
Just don't ask me how!
Yahoo!
Look at me!
No problem!
Piece of cake!
I think it's about time to teach him how
to control the fox's chakra.
Okay, out of the pool!
Come on in!
I'm gonna teach you a killer technique.
You are?
You're really?
You mean like something really powerful
and destructive?
Now then, there's something you need to
understand, kid, before we go any further.
I don't think you're even aware of it,
but you possess two chakras within you.
Huh?
Two chakras?
Haven't you ever felt the presence of a
different chakra?
Well, I'm not sure.
Hmm...
Oh, wait!
I do kind of remember.
There was this one time...
It was like all of a sudden
I had this weird upsurge
of power and I didn't
know where it came from.
I don't remember when it was exactly.
I almost thought it was a dream.
So I see.
But I do remember feeling that this was
something different than my usual chakra.
My normal chakra?
Well, if it was a color, it'd be blue.
But this was red.
Okay, that's enough training for today.
What, already?
What about that killer technique?
Come on!
I'm just getting started!
Let's go!
In training as in cooking, a watched pot
never boils.
Now, let's go back to town and have a real
bath, not one where you just fall in, okay?
This is better than falling in.
Nothing beats relaxing after a long day of
training.
Hey, hey, pervy sage!
So tell me about this killer technique.
Tomorrow is soon enough.
Ah, cheapskate!
We'd better get out soon.
Or we're going to be stuck with a giant
boiled toad.
Sorry, Ebisu.
It wasn't my plan to steal your student
from you.
Oh, that's of little importance.
Lord Hokage has had his ninja searching
for you everywhere.
We were just beginning to think that you
would never be found.
Then you turn up here, of all places,
right in front of me.
He will be pleased.
Have you told the Hokage you found me yet?
No.
Not yet.
Very good.
It's better that way.
You're after Orochimaru, aren't you?
No, unfortunately, I can't say that I am.
Sorry.
Huh?
The only thing that brought me here was the
chance of doing some research for a book.
I have no desire to get involved in any of
that other business.
What do you mean?
You can't be serious!
You know better than anyone!
There's only one way to deal with
Orochimaru.
He's one of the Sannin, the legendary
three ninja.
And he can only be stopped by the power of
another Sannin!
Your power, Master Jiraiya!
Don't you ever sleep at all?
Why are you here?
What do you want?
I was planning on attacking you while you
slept.
I already know all about your sand attack.
I wonder which is faster, your sand or my
sound?
When the moon is full... When
the moon is full, its blood boils.
What in the world are you?
Amazing.
So that's Gaara's true form, then,
is it?
I can't believe it.
A tailed beast brought into this village.
Well, there's certainly no denying its
power.
But are you actually able to control it?
At that level, yes.
But when the one tail transforms
completely and activates
his playing possum jutsu,
there's no stopping him.
All right, fine.
Then we'd better not agitate him any
further for now.
But I look forward to seeing him run amok
when the time finally comes.
Listen, is this okay?
He was a sound ninja.
Yes, it's fine.
He's long since served his purpose.
But I thought he was a guinea pig intended
to test the power of that kid, Sasuke.
What?
Is Kabuto in league with the sand ninja?
That's true.
Or it was.
It isn't necessary anymore.
See, the thing is, I was ordered to see
Sasuke when he was in the hospital.
But I... well, I failed in that mission.
Wait, what?
Yes, that's right.
They've discovered that I'm an agent of
the Sound Village.
I thought you were Orochimaru's right-hand
man.
But after being revealed to them, you just
nonchalantly come here and meet with me?
You're a fool.
Heh heh.
I let them find out.
Yes, I wanted to see just
how far the Hidden Leaf
Village would go when
they discovered the truth.
And even after they did, I knew it
wouldn't be too late to seize Sasuke.
It's a plan that was originally posed by
the Sound Village, so... if you guys are
gonna fail, then we'll have to back off
immediately.
Hmph.
The sand won't make a move till the last
moment.
This is the will of the Kazekai.
This can't be!
Very well.
This is the plan that you're to carry out.
Okay.
And remember, make sure you tell them
about this plan as soon as possible.
Yes.
I know.
All right.
Then I'll be going.
To think our ally, the Sand Village,
has a secret pact with the Sound Village!
I must tell Lord Hokage!
I'll take care of our little spy.
No, wait.
I will handle this.
As a gesture of faith
in our allegiance, the
least we Sand Ninja can
do is lend a helping hand.
Besides, it's just one little spy.
It'll be easy.
... ...
Grrr... Grrr...
Aahhh!
Achoo!
Ahhhhh!
Ha... Ha...
This is unexpected.
I thought that this fight would be settled
almost immediately.
I have to say, that Proctor was very slick
to slip past me the way he did.
Sheathing your sword.
Now!
Leaf-style crescent moon death!
My sword's stuck!
Your talent with a sword is superb.
Of course, stopping a physical sword is
easy and is only a rudimentary skill.
However...
A wind sword is a different story.
No one can stop it.
Ah!
We got you!
Oh!
Wow!
Good on you!
Knock it off!
Alright, Naruto.
I guess I'll teach you a technique now.
Well, it's about time and you better not
be kidding around here.
Okay, do you remember what we talked about
yesterday?
You know, that stuff about the two types
of chakra?
Huh?
We talked yesterday?
Very funny.
Remember you said something about having
different chakra?
One blue and one red?
Oh, yeah.
So what about it?
You said that when you exerted enormous
strength, you felt red chakra.
Yeah, that's right.
I don't know how else to describe it.
Alright, try building up that red chakra
right now.
Right now?
Well, I guess if you say so.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Well, did it work?
No, it's not right.
It's the same chakra as always.
Oh, man, you really have absolute zero
talent, don't you, kid?
Hey, don't go acting like you're so great.
And besides, I can't help it.
I mean, I don't even understand those two
types of chakra myself, alright?
Just keep trying.
I'm just trying.
Fine, I will.
Hmm.
So he doesn't understand it, huh?
Naruto probably still
hasn't realized that his
red chakra is really the
nine-tailed fox's chakra.
Judging by his story, it seems that the
excitement caused by danger and also
strong emotion are the keys to summoning
the nine-tailed fox chakra.
It's just no good.
I'm only getting the usual everyday chakra
here.
Hey, hold on a second.
Maybe I don't even need to summon the red
chakra.
I mean, what in the world
does it have to do with
the technique that you're
gonna teach me anyway?
Listen, boy.
For the technique I'm going
to teach you, the chakra
you've used until now is
nowhere near powerful enough.
If you want to use this technique,
you'll have to be able to pull out all the
stops and tap into the other
chakra that's been dormant
within you, summoning
it up at a moment's notice.
Yeah, that sounds really good.
Cool and exciting, but
how do you even know
that I really have that
chakra inside of me?
Oh, that's just what I wanted to hear.
Actually, it's because I am a sage.
Talk about giving an answer without giving
an answer.
Anyway, the special chakra that only you
have will become your greatest weapon,
I am sure of it.
Greatest weapon?
Really?
Yes, not using that is like wasting
treasure.
Look, there's no need to blindly follow
the same training.
You have two types of chakra, and don't
exhaust easily.
So you should learn to release the largest
amount of chakra you can, and then train
yourself so you can increase the total
amount of chakra you can use.
Once you do that, a whole world of jutsu
will open up to you.
Seriously?
Like what could I do?
Well, for example, the Summoning Jutsu
that I'm going to teach you.
Summoning?
That's right.
It is a teleportation technique in which
you sign a contract in blood with all
kinds of living creatures,
and then summon them
whenever you like with
Ninjutsu, your ninja art.
Oh yeah!
That sounds awesome!
Teach me quick!
Come on, right now!
Let's get going already!
Okay, just relax.
Before we begin, you're
going to need to use up all
your usual chakra so just
your red chakra remains.
All right!
Leave it to me!
So, he already knows the Shadow Clone
Jutsu.
Listen up!
All of us are going to have one great big
battle royale!
The last one left standing will be the
strongest me!
We're going to determine the me among me!
Get it?
Yeah!
Ah, now I see.
That's a pretty clever idea considering
he's so dumb.
Ah!
It seems that at long last you've finally
used up almost all your usual chakra.
Now I can teach you the technique.
Yes!
Oh man, I've been waiting for this all
day!
I couldn't tell.
All right, first I'm going to show you how
it's done.
Now watch carefully.
Summoning Jutsu!
Whoa, that is totally awesome!
That may be the coolest thing ever!
Go
ahead, open that scroll and take a look
inside.
It's a contract with the
summoning toads that's
been handed down from
earlier generations of ninja.
Just sign your name in your
own blood and stamp the
fingerprints of one hand in
blood beneath your signature.
Find the place where you want to summon
the creature.
Then build up chakra and press down the
hand you used on the contract.
That seal is Ino I Torisaru Itsuchi.
Here goes Naruto Uzumaki!
Okay, I'm all done, right?
What's next?
After burning off
your regular chakra, it
should be easier to
release your red chakra now.
So give it a try.
Quit bugging me, I already am!
Okay, Ino, I, Tori, Saru, Itsuchi...
Ninja Art Summoning Jutsu!
A tadpole?
Sure enough, this kid has no talent
whatsoever.
Hayate, what in the world happened to you?
Hey,
let's see how you like it!
Hey, Kirby Sage, hello!
Are you going to watch me try this jutsu
again or not?
Can't you see I'm busy with my research?
Do it yourself!
Okay, I will, and this time I'm going to
summon a frog the size of a house!
Summoning Jutsu!
Wait!
Give it a second, I think it's still
growing!
Listen, if you're not going to take this
seriously, then I'm through with you!
Do you understand me?
I am serious!
You're the one who's staring at the girls,
you old goat!
Stop fooling around and focus on your
chakras if your life depended on it!
What do you think I'm doing?
Some of you may not yet have heard the
news.
The body of Hayate Gekko was found near
Kikyo Castle.
What?
Hayate?
He's... he's dead?
Unbelievable.
This has to be Orochimaru's doing.
As likely as that may seem, let's not jump
to conclusions yet.
We think Hayate was on the trail of a
sound village spy named Kabuto.
No doubt Orochimaru is up to something,
but we don't know for sure if...
What I say, cancel the tuning exams and go
after Orochimaru.
No, I think not.
He revealed himself to Anka and sent a
warning not to cancel the exams.
You see, these exams have brought together
ninja from every allied nation.
What do you think it means?
There are two things we know about him.
That he bears an abiding
grudge against our
Hidden Leaf Village, and
that his power is great.
Perhaps great enough to crush a village on
his own.
Certainly great enough that any village
would prefer to have him on their side.
Rather than against them.
Impossible!
No village in the Alliance would betray
another and join forces with that fiend!
Well, the Alliance Treaty is only as
binding as any verbal agreement.
As we found out during the last Great
Ninja War.
In any case, until we're able to find out
more, this is all just idle speculation.
We've dispatched Anbu Black Ops to every
village to collect information.
We would be fools to act too hastily.
That might be just what our enemy is
aiming for.
And besides...
When and if the time comes,
we will gather the strength
of the Hidden Leaf
Village and fight if we must.
That's right, I should bring flowers!
Let's see now...
Oh no... Oh, Sakura,
you poor thing.
It's sad when a girl has to buy flowers
for herself.
I'm not!
I'm, uh... Not that it's
any of your business.
I didn't expect to find you minding the
shop.
I'll make this quick.
Taking a planter to the
hospital is like saying
you expect the person
to be there forever.
Some cut flowers might be a better idea.
Um...
Hospital?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb with me.
You're going there to visit Sasuke,
aren't you?
Hey, Mom!
I'm going out for a while.
Wait, what are you doing?
Get real.
If you think I'm gonna let you be the
first one to get in to see Sasuke,
you are so wrong.
Miss Ino-Pig, always butting in!
I think I'll bring him one red rose.
It's the flower of love.
Ha!
How lame can you get?
Me?
I'm gonna bring him a single daffodil.
A noble flower that bravely
endures the long months
of winter, then blossoms
forth as a sign of spring.
Just like you will soon blossom again,
Sasuke.
What are you, a botanist all of a sudden?
I warned you I will not lose out to you!
Whatever.
So are you gonna pay for that daffodil?
I should get two.
Two?
Why?
You trying to impress him?
One for him, and another for Lee.
Later!
More!
Ten orders of short ribs!
Man, you can put me off of food for good.
Just watching you makes me sick.
So, did you order the short ribs?
Ah, finally!
This is all mine, Shikamaru!
Don't try stealing any!
Don't worry, I wasn't planning on it.
What the heck are you guys doing?
Huh?
Ino!
Sakura!
Shikamaru, shouldn't
you be training for the
final exam instead of
sitting around pigging out?
I have been training.
Every day, all day.
Asuma's a goddamn slave driver.
And it's not only Shikamaru.
Choji's joined us for training as well.
What?
So you're going for it after all,
huh?
Mm-hmm!
Yeah!
And in return, I get all the barbecue I
can eat!
Well, that would explain it.
Oh, man.
I wish I'd never signed up for this stupid
final exam.
I don't want to hear it.
There are plenty of people who'd give
their right arm to be a part of it.
And besides, from
everything I've heard, Guy and
Kurenai's teams are
training their butts off.
Yeah?
Well, what about it?
After coming this far.
You don't want them making you look bad,
do you?
Man, this is such a drag.
I can't keep this up.
No human being could.
Think I've used too much of my chakra.
Neji!
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
I'll get with the tadpoles!
This is ridiculous, we're not getting
anywhere!
Look!
Can't you see it?
This one's bigger than the last one!
Who cares?!
It's still a tadpole!
Hahaha!
So you're here to see Sasuke Uchiha?
Please keep in mind that he's still very
weak.
He needs his rest.
You'll have to keep your visit short.
Five minutes, that's all I can give you.
All right.
Sasuke?
May I come in?
You have a couple of pretty visitors here.
Sasuke?
Sasuke!
All of his clothes are gone!
Huh?
This is terrible!
He's in no condition to be walking around
on his own!
Doctor!
Oh, Sasuke.
Where have you gone?
Huh?
What's up?
So you finally showed up.
Kakashi-sensei!
I want your help!
I need to get stronger!
Hmm.
This determination of Sasuke's... He's
dead serious.
It's Naruto.
He became so strong so fast.
I just can't waste any more time.
I see.
So that's it.
He finally took notice of the immense
power that Naruto has at his disposal.
I have a goal.
And to achieve it, I need to have more
power.
Okay.
Well, Sasuke, you know
about the five types of
chakra and about change
in chakra nature, right?
Yeah.
Members of the Uchiha
clan most often possess
fire nature and
specialize in fire style.
I already know that.
What's this about?
Some shinobi are able to affect more than
one change in chakra nature.
My chakra nature is lightning.
Sasuke, for a long time now I've had a
suspicion that you may be similar to me.
First, I'd like to verify what your chakra
nature is.
Looks like I may be able to pass my jutsu
onto you after all.
The unique jutsu of Kakashi the copy
ninja.
Lee?
Can we come in?
You have a couple of pretty visitors here.
Oh no!
Not Lee too!
Lee!
Weird.
Huh?
Look!
200 push-ups, that was the deal!
If you cannot finish them, it is 100 leg
squats, so come on!
Here we go!
190...
Lee!
You shouldn't be out of bed!
Stop it!
What do you think you're doing?
191...
Lee!
Keep away from me!
Please!
Got to... finish my training!
I should get two.
Two?
Why?
You trying to impress him?
One for him and another for Lee.
Oh...
Sakura, speaking of Lee, you heard the
news about him, didn't you?
Huh?
What news is that?
His injuries were bad.
Really bad.
It means that he'll never... well,
his days as a ninja are over.
195...
196...
197...
198...
Do not count me out!
I am not through yet!
You're right.
All the effort is pointless, if you don't
believe in yourself.
199...
199... 199...
Just one more... one more!
Just one more.
A little pause... and we are back.
He's here!
Today's history class will be outside.
As you're all aware, on this rock face are
the sculptures of the Hokages.
They're in order from the left.
There's the first, the second,
the third, and the fourth.
You probably could have figured that out.
The old man sure looks different up there
than he does now.
I mean, he used to have hair!
Iruka-sensei, so who's the fifth Hokage?
Hmm?
Hmm.
That hasn't been decided yet.
Maybe it'll be your favorite teacher!
Hmm.
So, working in an occasional joke to make
for an engaging history lesson, eh, Iruka?
Oh, Lord Hokage!
Whoa!
It's the third!
Hey, old man!
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to look at the mountainside
images like you students are doing.
Well, you've come at a great time!
Would you care to join me?
This is the man whose likeness is carved
up there on that mountain!
He's the great third Hokage!
Ah, just look at you.
You're all so young, unlike me.
There might be someone among you who will
take the name of Hokage.
Remember, you have just one life,
so don't choose a road that's impossible.
It doesn't matter what you do if you live
and die as you like.
No matter what route you
end up taking, remember
to protect the people
that are precious to you.
The people precious to us?
That's correct.
The ones you appreciate the very most.
And trust and love with all your heart.
Do you have people like that in your life?
Yeah, I do.
My dad and my mom.
And my big brother, even though I don't
like him much.
Oh yeah, and my dog Gunta.
I have some too.
My friends.
Me too.
So, do you have people like that too?
Yes, I do.
Of course.
Really?
Who?
Well, I have my grandson, Konohamaru.
And I also have all the people in this
village.
I'm sure you have your own.
Just as it was for you back then.
Come on, open your eyes already!
Hey, what was that for?
Oh, that?
To knock sense into you since you have
none.
I don't!
Look at you!
You've been training for three weeks and
you're still at this level?
If you continue like this, it's pointless.
Hey, that's not true!
Give me a break!
I'm trying as hard as I can here!
Maybe you are, maybe you're not.
If you want to succeed
at this summoning jutsu,
then you must do it like
your life depends on it.
What do you think I've been doing?
I train every day like I'm gonna die!
If you have time to complain about it,
teach me a trick to do it!
A trick?
Well, I don't know.
What?
You're not gonna teach me?
You need to put your life at risk.
My... life?
That's right, it's no joke.
Even so, are you willing to do it?
Of course!
I always risk my life!
There's no point in anything if you don't
go all the way!
I see... Huh?
Alright, follow me.
Hey,
if I do this, can I really summon a frog?
You bet!
Of course!
Absolutely!
Without a doubt!
Are you sure?
Is there anything else you've always
wanted to do?
Huh?
Anything?
What?
What are you... Gah!
To tap into his enormous chakra and use
it.
I'm certain that it's extremely difficult
to control that kind of power.
It's also true that
Naruto's body is too small a
vessel to contain the
nine-tailed fox's chakra.
It's likely that because
that chakra puts such a
burden on it, Naruto's
body normally suppresses it.
If the key to drawing out the nine-tailed
fox's chakra is danger and emotion,
he has to physically
experience them until
he can learn to summon
the chakra on his own.
Please forgive me for what I am about to
do, Fourth Okage.
...
Where... where are we?
Tell me...
Stand up!
What?
What's going on?
Your training ends right here.
Huh?
But I haven't done anything yet!
Naruto!
Starting now, you must stare death in the
face.
Death?
That's right.
To stave off the horror of death,
you must release enormous chakra.
Once you experience that, you'll
understand how to release the red chakra.
If you don't wish to die, do something
about it.
Now!
...
All right, Naruto.
Now we shall see if the strength that's
been given to you is a blessing or a curse.
...
If I don't grab onto something,
I'll die!
Now!
It is impossible, Naruto.
You have to recognize that.
The rocks are too slippery, and falling at
that speed with the limited control of
chakra that you possess, you can't
possibly cling to the rock.
Naruto, you must see it.
You can only depend on the chakra of the
Nine-Tailed Fox now.
This time, you have to turn the key
yourself.
If I go on like this, I really am gonna
die!
Die!
What?
Huh?
This feeling... it's the red chakra again!
What is this?
It's huge!
Come closer, little boy.
Um... How wonderful.
But this accursal gate confines me.
It's that infuriating sealing spell.
You're... you're the...
Nine-Tailed Fox!
Of course!
The red chakra is this guy's chakra!
Why are you here, foolish boy?
What do you want?
Or have you simply come to offer yourself
to me, so I might feast upon you narrowly?
Alright, look, you stupid fox!
You're in my body, and you owe me rent!
So for payment, I'll take your chakra!
You got that?
Well, I suppose I can't kill you,
can I?
After all, if you die, I die.
You're Grinch's most impressive little
boy.
Very well.
As a reward for making it this far,
I will loan you my chakra.
Huh?
This is it!
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Somebody just knew!
Well done, kid.
What's this?
Where in the world am I?
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
That was close.
Glad I got saved.
Course I could have done without the
falling on my neck part.
Look at that!
Awesome!
Man, that is humongous!
Wait, hold on here.
What's that?
This is... a toad, isn't it?
Let's see here...
There's no tail there!
I did it!
I didn't summon this... or this!
It's really... a real... toad!
Looks like he released the Chakra of the
Nine-Tailed Fox all on his own this time.
But still, I certainly can't say that he's
proficient at it yet.
He overdid it with the Chakra's power...
to have summoned him of all things.
You little snot!
Just whose head do you think you're
dancing around on top of anyway?
Well, let me tell you, I am the wise and
powerful Lord Gamabunta, the Chief Toad!
And you're an idiot!
Now shut up!
Ah!
What is this guy?
He seemed cool, but... give me a break
here!
Ah!
Just when I finally get to breathe some
fresh air again...
I find some weird kid tap-dancing on my
head!
Hey, Jiraiya!
Where are you, Jiraiya?
Just what do you think you're doing?
Whoa!
Well, this doesn't look good... Even
I'm not able to handle Gamabunta.
I mean, he's a real handful.
Jiraiya!
Show yourself, you baboon!
Hmm...
It would be a pain in
the neck if he found me
out, so I'd better
hightail it out of here.
Hey, little snot!
Uh, yeah?
Where's Jiraiya hiding?
Huh?
Who's this Jiraiya?
I don't know any...
Don't play dumb!
I'm talking about that lecher who calls
himself the Toad Sage!
Now where is he?
Well...
Man, he's scary!
Look, I'm giving you an
order, and if you can follow
it, I'll even consider
making you my henchman!
Now hurry up and answer me!
Okay, okay!
If you're talking about the Pervy Sage,
he's on the cliff up there, Chief Toad!
Up there?
Um, can I ask you one question,
Sir Toad, sir?
What is it?
What business do you have with that Pervy
Sage, anyway?
That's the very same question I want to
ask that pervert!
I mean, what in the
world does that fool want
with me, summoning me
to a dank place like this?
Oh, but, um... What now?
Well, actually, the funny thing is that
I'm the one who summoned you.
You see, I fell off the cliff, and I
thought that maybe you could rescue me, so.
..
Thanks, boss!
There's no way a little
squirt like you could
have enough power to
summon up a being like me!
Huh?
No, no, it's true, it's true!
I mean, I really, truly summoned you!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Knock it off, you Toad jerk!
You've been talking down to me and saying
whatever you want since you first got here!
But I'm the one who summoned you,
and that means I'm your master!
You have to start respecting me and doing
what I say!
You got that, Toad?
Hmm?
What was that?
You've got some nerve!
Who do you think you're talking to?
You!
A meaningless little squirt like you!
Barely old enough to stand, and you dare
to say to Lord Gamabunta, the Chief Toad,
that you're his master?
That's it!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Well, it looks like he reached the top
thanks to Gamabunta.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Whoa!
That was awesome!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
I hate to tell you this, you little snot!
But even if I were willing to believe that
you were actually the one who summoned
me... And trust me, kid,
that's a really, really big if.
If you're the kind of guy
who could fall off my back that
easily, then there's no way I
could ever accept you as my master!
You got it?
Hmm?
Now, since I'm back in the world,
after such a very, very long time...
If Jiraiya doesn't need me, I'm going for
a walk!
No!
Wait!
Listen, why don't you just get out of here
and go home?
Because it's clear you're incapable of
serving as my henchman!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
What?
What do you suppose you're doing now?
Fine, if making you respect me depends on
me staying on your back, well then...
I'll just make sure I don't get off your
back!
I'll keep your back the rest of the day no
matter what!
What?
That's right, and when
I do, then you'll have no
choice but to recognize me
as your undisputed master!
You really are a snot!
Fine if that's what you want, but don't
think I'm going to go easy on you!
You!
I must grip with chakra!
I don't have enough chakra!
Listen carefully, cheap-toed!
My name is Naruko Uzumaki!
I'm going to become Okage someday!
Don't forget that!
I don't care!
Welcome!
Come on in!
I am going to eat till I can't eat no
more!
Those guys are eating barbecue again.
Giving themselves a reward for training so
hard, I guess.
Hey, I thought you were told not to let
Gaara out of your sight, Konkuro.
Oh, don't worry.
Even someone like him wouldn't dare to do
anything in broad daylight.
But about you.
That guy Shikamaru would have...
Whatever his name is, he's the first guy
you're fighting, right?
Shouldn't you be formulating a battle
plan?
There's no way that I would lose to a guy
who's at that level.
No way.
You blew it, didn't you?
What?
If you had taken the
exam one year earlier, then
you would have made
Chunin easily, right, Tamari?
Don't say that.
What?
What did you just say?
I'm going to have you three ninja,
the best from the Hidden Sand Village,
participate in the upcoming Chunin exam.
But the reason that I'm having you do so
is not for you to pass the Chunin exam.
We must use this chance, so that we're
able to crush the Hidden Leaf Village.
But why?
Why are we turning on the Leaf Village?
Didn't we sign the Treaty of Alliance with
them?
Yes, we did.
And that treaty is the whole problem.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
You Genin aren't aware of all the details
of this.
But when the Treaty of Alliance was
signed, that idiot feudal lord who rules
us used it as an opportunity to force
military cutbacks on our village.
He also delegated to
the Hidden Leaf Village
matters that should
have been handled by us.
And even worse, he
significantly cut our village's
budget and slashed
the number of shinobi.
When the head of our country is weak,
we, the country's arms and legs, suffer.
And so we took the only choice left to us.
Improve the quality of every shinobi to
maintain our military strength.
That's why shinobi like you were created.
Gaara.
The Land of Wind's very existence is in
danger.
More danger than it's ever been in before.
But still, that idiot feudal lord and all
his incompetent advisors...
are too blind to see it.
So the Kazekage who detected this
weakening of the might of the Sand Village.
..
joined hands with the Sound Village to
show our feudal lord his stupidity.
By crushing the Hidden Leaf Village and
restoring our own, this needs to be done
to make that idiot aware of the importance
of preparing for a crisis.
If any more time
passes, our Sand Village
will be completely
drained of its abilities.
This is our only chance.
Now Gaara, this mission depends entirely
upon your skills.
Yes.
This is an A-plus ranked mission.
Make sure you succeed.
Okay.
Yes.
I'm bored.
The day sure goes by slowly when you're
not doing anything.
Not even much anything.
I guess.
Good work, Baki.
Thank you, Lord Kazekage.
I successfully moved all three ponds to
the final rounds as planned.
Hm.
And the pact with the Sound Village has
progressed as well?
Yes sir.
Hm.
Contains the details of the Sound
Village's plan.
Is there something else?
Well... What?
Out with it.
Yes, sir.
I was wondering if you
could position soldiers near
the border under the
pretext of a tactical exercise.
With just the four of us...
The Hidden Leaf Village
isn't full of Dimwits,
and the Anvu Black Ops
are active in that area.
If we do what you ask, they'll see right
through what we're planning.
Everything we work toward will be ruined.
But with only our current military
capability...
That's why I've sent Gaara and the others.
The restoration of Sound Village's glory
is in your hands.
Now... go.
Yes, sir.
How do you like that, Chief Toad?
I'm still on your back!
That's right!
I beat you!
No!
If he falls like that, he'll die!
Too bad for you, little snot.
And you almost made it, too.
Amazing.
He could hold out so long against a tough
opponent like Gamabunta.
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
You scoundrel, Jiraiya.
I am fully aware that this boy summoned me
all on his own.
He is courageous.
It's the first time since the fourth Hokage
that someone has dared to climb on my head.
As may be expected after that battle,
he looks completely drained of energy.
I don't mind giving him
some of my power, but I believe
that taking him to a place
of healing would be best.
What was that?
Huh?
So... you decided to wake up, huh?
Where am I?
What is this?
The hospital.
They said you've been out cold like this
for three days straight.
Three days?
I went to all the trouble
of getting this stuff for
Choji, and then the doctors
told me he couldn't have it.
Such a drag.
But at least we can eat it.
Choji?
You mean he's here in the hospital too?
Nothing to worry about.
All he's got is a bad case of indigestion.
He ate one short rib too many.
I should have figured.
That's just like him.
Yeah.
Well, you two are just lucky I'm around,
or you wouldn't have any visitors.
Here.
Oh, wow.
This looks delicious.
What?
What is it now?
Let's eat it in front of Choji.
It'll drive him crazy.
Man, that's mean.
I like it.
Why save him?
Because he's... he's my student.
And also because he is precious to me.
Oh, I see!
What am I?
I'm still starving!
Come on!
Don't torture me like that, Shikamaru!
I can't move... my body...
What the heck do you think you're doing in
here, you rat?!
Hey man, go easy!
I'm using my shadow
possession jutsu, so when
you're bashing him,
you're bashing me too.
You got it?
Oh, sorry, Shikamaru!
Hey Choji, feeling better?
Oh, Ino!
Alright!
A pretty girl with food!
This is my lucky day!
Well?
Are you gonna tell us what you were gonna
do?!
I was going to kill him.
What?
This guy's one cool customer.
Look at him.
He's not even phased by my shadow
possession jutsu.
You already beat him once in the
competition.
What's your problem?
Wasn't that enough for you?
Do you have some kind of personal grudge
against him or something?
It's nothing that complicated.
I simply want to kill him, that's all.
You know what?
You're sick in the head!
You're crazy!
Yeah.
You think we're gonna just stand by and
let you do whatever you want?
You sick selfish psycho.
This guy gives me the creeps.
There's always been something weird about
him.
Scary.
If he decides to make a move, I'm not sure
we'll be able to stop him.
If you don't stay out of my way,
I'll have to kill you too as well.
Oh really?!
Well let's just see you try it!
Hey, whoa kid!
Take it easy!
Best thing to do is try and bluff our way
out of this.
Yeah, yeah.
We watched your last match against Lee.
We know you're tough.
But you know, Naruto and I have a few
little tricks up our sleeves as well.
We were holding back during the
competition.
There are things you haven't seen yet.
On top of that, hey, it's two against one.
So don't be a fool, okay?
Just take my advice and go.
Quietly.
I'll say it once more.
If you get in my way, I'll kill you.
Okay, plan B.
And I'll say it again!
Let's see you try it!
Back off, will ya?
We don't want to go there!
This guy fights like he's mad,
like he's a demon or something.
He can act like a demon if he wants to,
but you know what?
I got the real thing inside of me!
Idiot.
Leave this to me.
What's the point of getting him mad?
A demon, huh?
My demon is as real as yours is.
From my birth, my upbringing was not what
most people would consider a happy one.
To ensure that I became the strongest of
shinobi, my father had cast his ninjutsu
on me, infusing my unborn self with a sand
spirit.
I destroyed the life of a woman who gave
birth to me.
I was born a monster.
Can it be true?
He's got one inside of him, too?
Gee, what a swell guy your dad must have
been.
He really must have loved you a lot.
You speak of love?
Don't measure me by your standards.
Love?
Family?
The only emotional ties I have to my family
are the ones I'd like to wrap around.
They're only ties of hate.
Given life by the death of
my mother, I was brought
into being and nurtured as
the salvation of the village.
I was the Kazekage child.
My father taught me the innermost secrets
of the shinobi.
He pampered and protected me, and left me
to myself.
For a time, I thought that was love.
Those who get to be too strong are apt to
become feared.
The jutsu that gave me birth had
unbalanced something in my mind.
Even the fools in my village finally
realized I had emotional problems.
My father, the Kazekage, had created me as
his ultimate weapon, but I eventually
became a threat to the very village I was
meant to save.
By the time I was six, I became a figure
of terror to the villagers.
To them, I was a relic of the past that
they wished would disappear.
So you see, I had failed at the one
purpose for which I was given life.
What then was left for me in this
existence?
Why go on living?
For a long time, I couldn't find an answer
to that.
But in order to live, you need a purpose.
To exist for no reason.
It's the same as being dead.
What is this guy talking about?
I know just what he means.
Exactly.
He's... he's the same as me.
Then in time, the answer came to me.
To put it simply, my reason for living is
in the killing of others.
For years, I lived in fear of those who
were sent to murder me.
But now I am at peace.
I killed many would-be assassins.
And it was while I was doing it that the
truth was made clear to me.
I live solely for myself.
I love only myself.
As it was the death of my mother that
first gave me life, now it is the death of
others that sustains me, that makes me
almost happy to be alive.
And there's no end to it.
As long as there are still people to kill
in this great, wide-crowded world.
I will never disappear.
This freak!
He's out of his mind!
I was alone, too.
I didn't know what I was here for,
why I was alive.
Until Iruka-sensei came along.
He saw what was in me.
He gave me a purpose, a reason for living.
But this guy had no one.
He had to find the answer on his own.
And this is what he came up with.
To kill in order to live.
Could I have ended up like that if...
We're so different, but we're so close to
being the same.
No!
I don't think I can beat this guy!
He shouldn't be able to do that.
Not with my Shadow Possession jutsu on
him.
I don't think I can beat him.
Hey, wake up!
Oh man, what a drag!
Naruto!
Now, let me feel alive.
Incoming!
Alright, that's enough.
Save it till tomorrow.
That's when the final competition begins.
Don't leave me alone.
I'm not bleeding, but it hurts a lot.
What am I?
All the same, I will kill you.
I'll kill you all.
Ah...
Whoa!
Oh!
One!
Two!
I love you!
Three!
My love for curry is never-ending.
Four!
Cheers!
Hooray!
All over the world, look!
We're having fun.
Let's look up in the sky.
Let's get up high.
Oh yeah!
A little pause... and we are back.